#### Contact

contact@tascott.co.uk

www.linkedin.com/in/tascott (LinkedIn) tascott.co.uk (Portfolio) tascottdev.wordpress.com (Blog)

### Top Skills

**HTML** 

React

CSS3

### Languages

English

# **Thomas Scott**

Javascript Developer

London, England, United Kingdom

## Summary

Adaptive front-end web developer experienced in JavaScript and with creating responsive applications. I am always interested in expanding my skillset.

In my current role I build new features using JavaScript, fix bugs and improve the speed and reliability of a web based web-app for the events industry. I am passionate about developing interfaces that are highly useful but also look beautiful.

I also have several years experience in customer service and sales working directly with customers and clients.

# Experience

Concise Interactive Event Apps 6 years 7 months

Frontend Developer

June 2019 - Present (3 years 10 months)

London, United Kingdom

Role expanded to include building new features and fixing bugs with a heavy emphasis on Javascript and Handlebars.js for templating with exposure to React and Node. Further developed jQuery, Node and CSS skills in an agile environment.

Junior Frontend Developer September 2016 - June 2019 (2 years 10 months) London, United Kingdom

The junior role at Concise incorporated custom styling and branding for an existing conference web-app which required a good knowledge of responsive design, HTML, SASS/CSS, Bootstrap and jQuery. Handlebars (templating) and Photoshop skills were honed.

I also worked for 3 months in New York at the company's principal US office as the primary Front-End Developer for Concise Apps in North America. In

Page 1 of 3

addition to my normal role I was tasked with training a colleague transitioning from technician to developer.

General Assembly
Web Developer - Student
April 2016 - July 2016 (4 months)
London

The intensive, three month Web Development Immersive course at General Assembly London taught me the skills required to become a full stack junior developer.

I worked across a range of technologies including the MEAN stack.

The course also incorporated many common industry practices such as TDD/BDD and Agile methodologies, as well as teaching valuable version control systems such as Github.

MyLondonHome
Property Consultant
September 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 1 month)
London, United Kingdom

Main responsibilities included building relationships with buyers looking for a property, assessing their requirements, conducting viewings, and of course, agreeing deals. Excellent people skills and the ability to listen to clients needs is paramount to guide them through the buying process.

### Education

#### edX

Trilogy's Skills Bootcamp in Front-End Web Development, Computer Software Engineering · (November 2022 - March 2023)

#### **General Assembly**

Web Development Immersive (Full Time), Web Development · (2016 - 2016)

University of Liverpool BA, Geography (2009 - 2012)

Finchley Catholic High School High School, Geography, Psychology, (2001 - 2008)